

### CONTACT



Hyderabad, India 91



**l** 8008213546



anjalimarch24@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/anjalimishra-38494925

# **SKILLS**

- · Software Testing: Functional Testing, **Automation Testing**
- · Testing Framework: TestNG, Jasmine, Mocha, Cucumber
- · Design Patterns: Page Object Model, Behaviour Driven Development
- Functional Testing Tool: Selenium WebDriver/Grid, Protractor, Webdriver IO, Cypress
- · API Testing Tool: Rest Assured
- · Technologies/Domain: US Tax Process, Hospitality, Fleet Management System
- · Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, Apache POI
- · Web Technologies: Angular JS, Node.JS
- Scripting: Java, JavaScript
- · IDE: Eclipse, VS Code
- Testing Framework: TestNG, Jasmine, Mocha
- · Web Debugging Tool: XPath, Firepath, Firebug
- Build Tool: Maven
- · Processes: Agile-Scrum, Waterfall
- · Bug Tracking Tools: JIRA, VSTS, QTest
- · Continuous Integration Tools: Jenkins, Azure Devops
- · Version Control: GIT, SVN, BitBucket
- DataBase: SQL Server
- Operating Systems: Windows

# Anjali Mishra

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven Senior Consultant with 6 years' experience in Software Quality Assurance Testing. Adept in collaborative problem solving, risk management and creative solutions. Advanced background in anticipating user behaviours and providing the solution to improve product quality for various software applications.

# **WORK HISTORY**

### Senior Consultant

06/2021 - Current

### Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited - India

- Championed continual process improvements at board meetings by offering 6 years' industry experience and expertise.
- Troubleshot complex operational issues by diagnosing root causes and devising effective solutions.
- Encouraged development of clear objectives and action plans.
- Drafted Test Plan which included testing objectives, testing phases, scenarios, and test environment after thorough analysis of business rules.
- Involved in test cases review by development team, and product management and modified test cases based on their feedback.
- Responsible for planning, executing, and managing UI automation scripts for AngularJS applications using Webdriver IO and Mocha Testing Framework to provide better regression test coverage.
- Created manual test cases, and reviewed with different stakeholders to validate functionality, so that it meets expected business criteria.
- Performed functional testing to identify various critical points in application.

#### Consultant 06/2018 - 06/2021

### **Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited** - India

- · Participated in requirement understanding and developing use cases.
- · Drafted functional scenarios and test cases to provided better coverage of functional requirements and reviewed with team lead.
- · Shared test reports with various test metrics with team members and team lead, to have clarity on quality control.
- · Automated functional test cases by using Selenium Web-Driver and TestNG testing tools.
- Developed scripts for data driven framework using Selenium WebDriver, TestNG and Apache POI API.
- Used Maven to build and to run Selenium automation framework which consists 100 scripts shared consolidated automation test reports, which saved 2 weeks of manual effort.

# Software Testing Engineer Cybage Software - India

04/2016 - 06/2018

- Effectively determined automation testing needs through Selenium Webdriver.
- Continually improved team processes from Requirement Gathering to Test
  Closure
- Utilised JIRA and VSTS to perform manual testing through test suites.
  Participated in all phases of Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), its methodologies such as Agile, SCRUM.
- Involved in understanding business requirements of customer and developed test cases.
- · Developed, modified, and executed scripts.
- Implemented Generic Functions and Project specific Functions in Libraries, in Automation test framework built using Page Object Model design pattern.
- Customized scripts using parameterization techniques to save increase efficiency of framework by 30%.

# **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Technology**: Computer Science And Engineering, 07/2008 **Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University** – Lucknow

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

**Applause Award** 2022

- Got Applause award for automating Mylnsight CE using Webdriver IO. **Innovation Champion Award** 2021
- Got recognized for building a proof of concept for automating webservices using Rest Assured.

Spot Award 2019

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

· ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level